theoremreach.com 2016-04-04

# TheoremReach Consumer Sampling

### TheoremReach Privacy Policy

TheoremReach is a market research and surveying company that works with companies such as advertisers and market researchers to poll people on their opinions and preferences. TheoremReach believes in and respects the sanctity of your privacy.

The information we collect is typically used in aggregate form to help companies understand marketplace needs as well as to create and deliver better products and services. We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information.

### What do we collect?

We collect the responses that you submit to our multiple choice surveys. In rare instances, we may ask if you want to provide your email address and/or mobile phone number for additional follow-up. If we do this, it is for our own internal use only, unless we explicitly list who the information will be passed through to, such as if you opt to visit a Lexus dealership for a test drive. We will never disclose your information to any other company entity without disclosing it to you, unless required by law.

### How do we use these responses?

We analyze and aggregate them to find insights and trends in groups of responses, for advertisers, market researchers, and polling parties, such as for election estimates or to see if people like Coca Cola or Pepsi more.

Survey Response Data. We may sell, license, or share the Survey Responses and Response Metadata (collectively, the “Response Data”) and related information with survey creators and researchers (i.e., our customers). We may aggregate your Response Data with Response Data collected from other users through the Services and share such aggregated data with third parties, including our advisors, investors, and/or customers. Additionally, we may share Response Data we collect with third parties in connection with the use and operation of the Services and other aspects of our business (e.g., with our customers, agents, advisors, consultants, advertisers, business partners, investors and/or vendors).

### Can you access your responses?

If you wish to access, modify, or remove your historic responses at any point in time, simply email privacy@theoremreach.com and include your device ID with a message letting us know what you would like us to do with your responses.

### Personal Information about Respondents

In the course of responding to our surveys, you may have the opportunity to voluntarily submit personally identifiable information (e.g., e-mail address or mobile phone number). TheoremReach maintains this information in a database, and may use this information to invite you to participate in future surveys, subject to agreement with the authoring and the respondent-providing client and your explicit opt-in to receive e-mail or mobile communications. Your decision to participate in future surveys is completely at your discretion. That is, you have no obligation to complete this or any future survey. By participating in a survey you understand and consent to this policy.

### Notice to Children and Young People

TheoremReach does not collect nor keep personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.

### Use of Cookies and Device IDs

To invite you to participate in surveys that may be of great interest to you and to enable you to use our service, we use a hashed version of your device ID -- a unique identifier of your mobile device that is coded and anonymized. In some cases, when you take our survey from a mobile browser, we will place “cookies” on your mobile device. Cookies are small text files that your browser stores on your device and are commonly used by web sites to provide you with an enhanced experience by remembering you from previous visits. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they enable us to understand the surveys you may have taken. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to inform you or prevent the use of cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able, depending upon the individual survey, to complete more than the first set of questions in a survey. 

If you would like to opt-out from either storing your device ID or accepting our cookies, or if you would like to opt out of both of these enhancements, click here.

### Log Files

Like most online and mobile companies, we log the use of our service. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks in order to administer the survey, track aggregate movement, analyze trends, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Disclosure of Information

When you supply any personally identifiable information, such as an email address or phone number, during the course of completing a survey it may be shared with a third party company who has been hired by us to provide services to help us with our business activities such as product fulfillment and follow-up information. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

### Confidentiality

We are sensitive to the privacy and security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee absolute security as such information may be transmitted using the Internet, other public telecommunication networks, servers, hardware or software ("systems") that are not owned, operated, or controlled by us.

### Compliance with Legal Proceedings

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served to us.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this policy, TheoremReach, general online and mobile practices, or how we survey, please feel free to reach us at admin@theoremreach.com.
